<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="webSite"><u>Website</u></string>
    <string name="information"><u>Information</u></string>
    <string name="rightLeftArrow">Indicates that user can scroll in the indicated direction</string>
    <string name="upDownArrow">Extends and collapses text</string>
    <string name="placeImage">Image for specific place</string>
    <string name="locationIcon">Indicates user can open maps for specific place</string>
    <string name="webIcon">Indicates user can open website of specific place</string>

    <string-array name="ToSleepAroPalace">
        <item>Aro Palace</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>Bulevardul Eroilor 27</item>
        <item>https://aro-palace.ro</item>
        <item><p>Located in the center of the country, Aro - Palace is a recognized leader on the
            domestic and international tourism market, with accommodation and public catering
            services at a high - quality standard.</p></item>
        <item>45.645385, 25.590911</item>
        <item>https://aro-palace.ro/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/hotel-aro-1.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToSleepResidenceHirscher">
        <item>Residence Hirscher</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>Apollonia Hirscher 14</item>
        <item>http://www.residence-hirscher.eu/</item>
        <item>Either on business or leisure trip, for one day, one week or more, we invite you to enjoy 
            the comfort of a modern equipped apartment, situated in the Old Centre of Brasov.</item>
        <item>45.640472, 25.589936</item>
        <item>http://residence-hirscher.pe-piata.ro/images/R-H_hirscher.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToSleepHotelKolping">
        <item>Hotel Kolping</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Petofi Sandor 27</item>
        <item>http://hotel.kolping.ro/</item>
        <item>Located at the foot of the Tâmpa Mountain, in the Historic Centre, at a distance of 
            800m from the Black Church, our hotel is an ideal place for business and leisure 
            tourism as well.</item>
        <item>45.634707, 25.586986</item>
        <item>http://www.brasovhoteluri.ro/wp-content/galerie_foto/hotel-kolping-brasov/hotel-kolping-brasov-7.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToSleepBelvedere">
        <item>Belvedere</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>Stejerisului 11</item>
        <item>http://hotelbelvederebv.ro/</item>
        <item>We invite you to spend a few days, choosing between the generous space of an apartment 
            or the privacy that a standard room will give you with a superb view over the mountains.
            You will find a tender feeling of comfort and good taste in the interior spaces. The
            memories of days spent here will make you come back over and over.</item>
        <item>45.645229, 25.578645</item>
        <item>http://www.viaromania.eu/pictures/accommodation/images/61/hotel-belvedere-brasov-490.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToSleepResidenceAmbient">
        <item>Residence Ambient</item>
        <item>3.7</item>
        <item>Castanilor 3</item>
        <item>https://www.residenceambient.ro/en/</item>
        <item>Located very close to historical center of Brasov , Ambient Residence is perfect for 
            exploring one of Europe’s best preserved medieval cities. With us, you can enjoy a
            comfortable, modern and cozy rooms in the city at the best Ambient price.</item>
        <item>45.649003, 25.603929</item>
        <item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/04/b4/ff/09/residence-ambient.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToSleepCoroana">
        <item>Coroana</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
        <item>Republicii 62</item>
        <item>http://aro-palace.ro/hotel-brasov-coroana-en.html</item>
        <item>Hotel Coroana is one of the architectural jewels of Brasov, being the oldest hotel in 
            the city, the meeting place of great personalities of the time. Placed on the city’s 
            famous pedestrian street, the hotel attracts all gazes through the Art Nouveau and
            Baroque architecture, being a historic monument.Architects Schuller and Goldsmidt were 
            inspired by the Munchen architecture, suggesting a symbolic building that pleased both 
            aesthetically and functionally.</item>
        <item>45.644189, 25.594438</item>
        <item>http://www.cazari.ro/upload/unitReserv/b_brasov_brasov_oras_hotel_coroana_32353.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToSleepLongStreet">
        <item>Long Street</item>
        <item>4.0</item>
        <item>Lunga 193</item>
        <item>http://www.longstreethotel.ro/en/</item>
        <item>Every room of the new Long Street Hotel, located near the tourist sights of Brasov
            (Piata Sfatului and its famous pedestrian street, Black Church, Brasov Citadel, Black
            Tower, Aqua Park-Aqua Paradise, Icco Clinic and Oncological Hospital, exit to the
            Poiana Brasov, Gara and Autogara towards Bran).</item>
        <item>45.657555, 25.580825</item>
        <item>https://infohoteluri.blob.core.windows.net/imagini/hotel-long-street-brasov-brasov/brasov_hotel-long-street__11f2f27b-b6c7-49a4-80c3-f3d231cb6297.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToEatOldJackBurgerHouse">
        <item>Old Jack Burger House</item>
        <item>4.0</item>
        <item>Piata Sfatului 7</item>
        <item>https://oldjackburgerhouse.ro</item>
        <item>Let\'s eat like mobsters. We serve breakfast, burgers, ribs, steak, salads and, of
            course, desert. Enjoy! There’s a new place in town, where the best of the best have 
            gathered for a common purpose. A place where they get the respect they deserve. A 
            place where YOU get a taste of the real deal. Here come the ones who always have it 
            their way. Who know what they want and how to get it. A place where it feels like
            family. A different kind of family.</item>
        <item>45.642572, 25.589823</item>
        <item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/12/13/e7/f3/photo0jpg.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToEatPilvax">
        <item>Pilvax</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Michael Weiss 16</item>
        <item>http://www.pilvax.ro/en/</item>
        <item>The Pilvax Restaurant is our families dream come true. This is the reason why our 
            goal is to create a familiar, cosy atmosphere. The name of our restaurant was inspired
            by a well known coffee house from Budapest, the Pilvax Coffee-House, which opened its 
            doors at the beginning of the XIXth century. Ever since, it welcomes its guests with
            the same devoted attention. We hope, during the time spent here, You will be part of 
            a harmonious and hospitable atmosphere, as well as of a gastronomical delight, among 
            your family and/or friends.</item>
        <item>45.643671, 25.590809</item>
        <item>https://belgianfoodie.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Brasov-Pilvax-Dessert-min-e1466416410574.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToEatTheHockeyPub">
        <item>The Hockey Pub</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Nicolae Balcescu 12</item>
        <item>http://www.thehockeypub.ro/</item>
        <item>All you need from a pub. Great atmosphere, good food, big selection of drinks.
            Ideallylocated in the center of the city, friendly staff, plenty of room and several 
            TVs toenjoy a game. The beverage selection is quite extensive and reasonably priced. 
            And mostof all, it has an unique touch, with all the hockey memorabilia which sets it 
            apart from most other places.</item>
        <item>45.641573, 25.592210</item>
        <item>https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSPSYhv14Vhyt6de49ZFGK11d_OH28_YLguf4OZAXO8N8odJhdw</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToEatGott">
        <item>Gott</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Gott Johann</item>
        <item>http://hotelgott.ro/ro/restaurant-italian-brasov.html</item>
        <item>No description</item>
        <item>45.641302, 25.589797</item>
        <item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/02/cb/6a/06/gott-pub.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToEatSimone">
        <item>Simone</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Politehnicii 6</item>
        <item>No website</item>
        <item>Situated right in the heart of town, but quite far from the urban noise of the main
            road, we would present our Bistro as an oasis. Our kitchen has its urban type, is
            multicultural, young and fresh. Our homemade plates are prepared on site in respect and
            in harmony with the seasons, with priority on the local products and inspiration from
            all cultures around the world. Thus, our food here is prepared with fruit and vegetables
            gathered daily at the market on the day. During the day you can give peace and rest to
            your mind's eyes, while during the weekend you can dance the night away at our coolest parties. </item>
        <item>45.643441, 25.596127</item>
        <item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/d4/80/03/ruben-sandwich.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToEatTerroirsBoutiqueDuVin">
        <item>Terroirs Boutique du Vin</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Postavarului 2</item>
        <item>http://terroirs.ro/</item>
        <item>Wine boutique and bar with a selection of international meals. Non smoking, kids
            are welcomed.More than 400 wines from all over the world.</item>
        <item>45.641940, 25.590976</item>
        <item>https://3so0ss2mrjqz30wj9q48we8j-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/brasov/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2017/04/Terroirs-Boutique-du-Vin2.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToEatLaCeaun">
        <item>La Ceaun</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Piata Sfatului 11 - 12</item>
        <item>https://laceaun.com/</item>
        <item>Small traditional restaurant serving mainly soups and stews, cooked fresh every day 
            with local ingredients</item>
        <item>45.642210, 25.589745</item>
        <item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/d5/97/5c/ciorba-de-fasole-cu-ciolan.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToEatSergiana">
        <item>Sergiana</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Muresenilor 28</item>
        <item>https://www.sergianagrup.ro/restaurante/restauranant-sergia</item>
        <item>Sergiana Group encompasses a farm and a livestock complex in the vicinity of Brasov, 
            a network of 54 stores with its own distribution system, as well as the best restaurants
            in Brasov, and an event center - Sergiana Center. Everything built on a desire to offer
            customers quality food and Romanian products - perfectly controlled, from their basic
            ingredients to the way they’re sold in shops.</item>
        <item>45.645418, 25.589804</item>
        <item>https://www.brasovtour.com/pictures/restaurant-sergiana/zA6425Az56_sergiana8.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToEatRawdia">
        <item>Rawdia</item>
        <item>4.7</item>
        <item>Apollonia Hirscher 7</item>
        <item>http://rawdia-brasov.ro</item>
        <item>Love, the rest are ingredients</item>
        <item>45.640589, 25.590144</item>
        <item>https://scontent-frx5-1.cdninstagram.com/vp/dc3d279a5bc1da254eb6fb02fc036a4c/5B28BC7D/t51.2885-15/e35/28427723_539397909765797_3517850821293244416_n.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToVisitBlackChurch">
        <item>The Black Church</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Yard of Johannes Honterus 2</item>
        <item>Biserica Neagră or Black Church (Romanian: Biserica Neagră) is a church in Brașov, a
            city in south-eastern Transylvania, Romania. It was built by the German community of the
            city and stands as the main Gothic style monument in the country, as well as being the
            largest and one of the most important Lutheran (Evangelical Church of Augustan
            Confession in Romania) places of worship in the region.</item>
        <item>45.641113, 25.587777</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/c/ca/Biserica_Neagra%2C_Brasov%2C_Romania.jpg/1200px-Biserica_Neagra%2C_Brasov%2C_Romania.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToVisitPelesCastle">
        <item>Peles Castle</item>
        <item>4.7</item>
        <item>Aleea Peleșului 2, Sinaia</item>
        <item>Peleș Castle (Romanian: Castelul Peleș is a Neo-Renaissance castle in the Carpathian 
            Mountains, near Sinaia, in Prahova County, Romania, on an existing medieval route 
            linking Transylvania and Wallachia, built between 1873 and 1914. Its inauguration was 
            held in 1883. It was constructed for King Carol I.</item>
        <item>45.360108, 25.542587</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/6/6d/Castelul_Peles%2C_Sinaia_-_Vedere_panoramica.jpg/1200px-Castelul_Peles%2C_Sinaia_-_Vedere_panoramica.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToVisitBranCastle">
        <item>Bran Castle</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>General Traian Moșoiu 24, Bran</item>
        <item>Bran Castle (Romanian: CastelulBran), situated near Bran and in the immediate vicinity
            of Brașov, is a national monument and landmark in Romania. The fortress is situated on
            the border between Transylvania and Wallachia.The castle is now a museum dedicated to 
            displaying art and furniture collected by Queen Maria. Tourists can see the interior on 
            their own or by a guided tour. At the bottom of the hill is a small open-air museum park
            exhibiting traditional Romanian peasant structures (cottages, barns, etc.) from across 
            the country.</item>
        <item>45.515158, 25.367121</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Castelul_Bran.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToVisitNarrowStreet">
        <item>Narrow Street</item>
        <item>No rating</item>
        <item>Strada Sforii</item>
        <item>Heading into Brasov through Poarta Schei, the third street on your right is Strada
            Sforii, allegedly the narrowest street in Europe. It dates from the 18th century and,
            less than a metre wide, is perhaps the only street in Romania where you can touch both
            sides with your hands at the same time.</item>
        <item>45.639837, 25.588505</item>
        <item>https://i.pinimg.com/236x/94/40/88/944088ead461d52a9e8268a38a4bc1a4.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToVisitParcCentral">
        <item>Parc Central</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>Nicolae Iorga</item>
        <item>Brasov is blessed with a large, well-tended park in the very heart of the city. In
            summer, when the flowers are in full bloom it really is a picture postcard kind of place.
            There is a good children’s playground, complete with bouncy slides and bouncy castles,
            there is an area where old men get together for serious games of chess. There are two
            buildings of note on the edge of the park, both masterpieces which date to the end of
            the 19th century, when the Hungarians ruled these lands. </item>
        <item>45.646124, 25.591781</item>
        <item>http://virtual-tourist.ro/images/parcul_central/parcul_Nicolae_Titulescu_brasov.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToVisitFirstRomanianSchool">
        <item>First Romanian School</item>
        <item>4.7</item>
        <item>Piata Unirii 2 - 3</item>
        <item>Once upon a time was a Romanian school where young people first learn to become 
            notaries, teachers and priests. The beginnings of the school could be somewhere in the 
            XIth – XIIth centuries. A proof is a manual of 700 pages called “Omiliar” a book about 
            virtues, a sign that above all, the school teaches you to be human. Certainly, the 
            school existed there in 1399, because that year, Pope Boniface speaks “about followers 
            (students) from Schei Braşov, who were taught by pseudo teachers”.</item>
        <item>45.636112, 25.581169</item>
        <item>http://cyd.ro/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/prima-scoala-romaneasca-12.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToVisitCatherineGate">
        <item>Catherines Gate</item>
        <item>4.6</item>
        <item>Enter from Poarta Schei</item>
        <item>Catherine\'s Gate (Romanian: Poarta Ecaterinei) in Braşov, Romania, was built by the
            Tailors’ Guild, in 1559 for defensive purposes instead of an old gate destroyed by the 
            flood in 1526. It is named after St. Catherine's Monastery that was situated here in 
            former times. It is the only original city gate to have survived from medieval times. 
            In fact the central tower is only a part of the original gate; documents talk about the
            existence of a wooden structure which was demolished in 1827. The original structure can
            be seen at the Weaver's Bastion where the large model of Braşov in 1600 is displayed.</item>
        <item>45.639713, 25.586080</item>
        <item>http://www.zilesinopti.ro/media/b67926fcafde264553101351e648294e.jpg/resize?w=750</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToVisitBlackAndWhiteTowers">
        <item>White &amp; Black Towers</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>Little hike from Dupa Ziduri </item>
        <item>Two small towers keep watch over old Brasov from the Warthe hill on the northern side
            of the city: the so-called White and Black towers. While not identical (the white tower,
            above, is much larger) - were nevertheless built at the same time, late in the 15th century.</item>
        <item>45.643144, 25.586480</item>
        <item>http://www.zilesinopti.ro/media/71440051057bc38868800b2.50559607.jpg/resize?w=750</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToDoHikingBucegi">
        <item>Bucegi Mountains (Omu Peak – 2505m)</item>
        <item>http://muntii-bucegi.ro/en/acces-way/</item>
        <item>The Bucegi mountains own their fame to the spectacular landscapes and the accessibility 
            of their routes. Well known for hiking, winter sports and climbing, these mountains are 
            high compact blocks, edged by steep slopes which dominate the Prahova Valley (Busteni, 
            Sinaia, Predeal) a popular land for its mountain resorts. At a higher elevation is the 
            Bucegi Plateau, where wind and rain have turned the rocks into spectacular figures such 
            as the Sphinx, a rock with the shape of a human-like face, with a lingering and enigmatic 
            smile and Babele( the old ladies).</item>
        <item>http://infotravelguide.ro/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/varfulomu3.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToDoHikingPostavaru">
        <item>Postavaru Mountain (Postavaru Peak – 1799m)</item>
        <item>http://www.discoverpoiana.ro/en/drumetii-montane/</item>
        <item>It is not very high, thus not as spectacular as other mountains in the Carpathians, 
            but it has some good ski slopes and beautiful scenery. Postavaru Mountain is ideal for 
            winter sports with 150 hectares of specific equipment and facilities, ski tracks of 
            various degrees of difficulty, an artificial snow track provided with night lighting 
            and a skating rink. The name of the resort at the foot of Postavaru is Poiana Brasov 
            and it is considered the best skiing resort in Romania.</item>
        <item>http://www.catalinenache.eu/wp-content/uploads/2009/09/varful-postavarul-1799m-altitudine-fotograf-catalin-enache-03.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToDoHikingPiatraMare">
        <item>Piatra Mare Massif (Piatra Mare Peak – 1844m)</item>
        <item>http://www.wandermap.net/ro/route/2868435-dambu-morii-drumul-familiar-cabana-piatra-mare-vf-piatra-mare/#/z13/45.5637034,25.6760788/terrain</item>
        <item>Despite providing fewer tourist facilities (chalets, hotels, cable car) than its
            neighbor, the Postavaru Mountain, Piatra Mare (106 sq km) lasts in the memory of generations
            of tourists for its wonderful landscapes. Among its attractions are the huge, spectacular,
            yet difficult to climb steep Eastern slopes, the wild Sapte Scari (Seven Steps) Canyon,
            visited by scores of tourists from spring through autumn, the Tamina Waterfall. The Sapte
            Scari Brook falls into Sipoaia basin at a 60 m level difference over a small distance of
            160 m. In this area, the valley sides are almost vertical, very close to each other,
            and polished by the falling water.</item>
        <item>http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-eJMd9fxS5a4/VXwZgXuZiKI/AAAAAAAAB0g/D3vA6wXCnq0/s1600/_DSC9027_stitch.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToDoHikingPiatraCraiului">
        <item>Piatra Craiului Mountain (La Om Peak – 2237m)</item>
        <item>https://www.uncover-romania.com/attractions/nature/piatra-craiului-national-park/</item>
        <item>Piatra Craiului-The Royal Rock-is probably Romania’s most loved mountain especially by 
            hikers and nature lovers. It is a beautiful limestone ridge from where you have superb
            views over the surrounding country. The shining glow of this huge white limestone ridge 
            can be seen from afar and it is probably the source of its unusual name.</item>
        <item>http://muntii-nostri.ro/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/2MN_img_Creasta-Nordica-a-Pietrei-Craiului-si-Orga-Mare-20-1024x685.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToDoHikingCiucas">
        <item>Ciucas Mountains (Ciucas Peak – 1954m)</item>
        <item>http://muntii-nostri.ro/en/munte/muntii-ciucas-2/</item>
        <item>Ciucas Mountains, easily accessible mountains, lie on a secondary road to Brasov,
            providing a fascinating ridge dotted with landforms of exceptional beauty, fashioned
            in limestone and conglomerates. These mountains present an extraordinary rich and varied
            relief, rarely encountered in the Romanian Carpathians. The upper part reveals a unique
            association of towers, needles, columns, mushrooms, bare rocks and sphinx-like forms.</item>
        <item>http://static3.evz.ro/image-original-605-388/cache/2016-09/muntii-ciucas-465x390.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ToDoHikingFagaras">
        <item>Fagaras Mountains (Moldoveanu Peak – 2545m)</item>
        <item>https://travelguideromania.com/fagaras-mountains-the-highest-mountains-in-romania/</item>
        <item>Also known as the “Transylvanian Alps”, as a 19th century traveler called them, the 
            Fagaras are truly the highest, largest, widest, rockiest and most impressive mountain 
            range in Romania, whether we are talking about extreme skiers, rock climbers, regular 
            mountaineers or people interested in a nice and quiet place in the middle of the nature.</item>
        <item>http://bloguldecalatorii.ro/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/DSC07982-1080x720.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToDoParcAventura">
        <item>Parc Aventura</item>
        <item>4.7</item>
        <item>Paltinului 16 </item>
        <item>http://www.parc-aventura.ro/en/</item>
        <item>The adventure park is an outdoor sports and leisure activity, a very good way to 
            spend your free time with your family and friends.</item>
        <item>45.614268, 25.637492</item>
        <item>http://www.parc-aventura.ro/images/parc-aventura2.png</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToDoAquaticParadise">
        <item>Aquatic Paradise</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>B-dul Grivitei, 2F-2G</item>
        <item>http://www.paradisulacvatic.ro/en/</item>
        <item>Aquatic Paradise opened in July 2007 and meets all requirements for a genuine health 
            and leisure center, as it is spread over a covered area of 12000 sqm and another 12000 
            sqm open air for the warm season.</item>
        <item>45.6733739, 25.586012</item>
        <item>http://www.paradisulacvatic.ro/files/gallery/galerie-foto-paradisul-acvatic/im_10015.jpeg</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="ToDoEscapeRooms">
        <item>Escape Rooms</item>
        <item>4.3</item>
        <item>Castelului 52</item>
        <item>http://escaperoomsbrasov.com/?lang=en</item>
        <item>First you book a room… \n …then you come to our location… \n
			…we lock you down… \n …and you have 60 minutes to escape. If you can😉.</item>
        <item>45.640041, 25.590796</item>
        <item>http://img.escaperoomsbrasov.com/2015/03/logo-lacat-3.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
